Speak.
Are you a rebel?
What is your relationship with our lord?
I
was making contact
with Director
Chu.
Lord Chu will be here to interrogate you shortly.
Say exactly what I taught you.
Hand this to her.
I guarantee you will live.
Assassinate the Emperor.
Nonsense!
Stop.
This really is a secret letter from a traitor
intending to assassinate His Majesty.
Feng Xiu,
it's you.
We have both witnesses and material evidence.
How dare you deny it?
Chu Sanniang,
detain her on the spot.
I will report to Lord Zhou immediately.
Lord Feng.
How dare you block Lord Zhou's attendant?
Do you have a death wish?
Step aside.
You two,
come here.
Beast.
My good Commander.
I never thought
you'd see this day.
Disobeying a superior's orders,
colluding with rebels and assassins.
Oh.
Now there is one more:
brutally murdering a colleague.
With three crimes combined,
now,
you are doomed for good.
Chu Sanniang.
Lady Chu.
I served you tirelessly,
and always looked out for you.
But what about you?
You always looked down on me.
Now you know.
The entire Bingjingwu will belong to me, Feng Xiu.
The Tanshisi is here to take over the traitor.
Where is the traitor?
Commander Cui.
Chu Sanniang colluded with the traitor
with the intent to assassinate the Emperor.
And to cover for the traitor,
she murdered her colleagues.
All witnesses and material evidence are at the scene.
Please, Commander Cui,
investigate thoroughly.
Listen up, everyone.
Arrest Chu Sanniang
and all the rebels in the Bingjing Office.
Yes.
Go.
Hurry up and run!
Look.
She is in trouble indeed.
Brother Chaijiu,
we have to escape.
I see someone in the next cell.
Let's put on their clothes.
Find a way to knock them out.
You...
You are out already?
Untie me too.
The rebel Chu Sanniang
colluded with and harbored assassins,
and killed Feng Xiu and other fellow members.
I am ordered by Prime Minister Cai
to arrest the rebels.
Cui Hong.
The Bingjing Office
is directly supervised by the Emperor for major cases.
Even though we both belong to the Imperial City Department,
the Bingjing Office is on equal footing with your Tanshi Office.
What right do you have
to convict me?
Chu Sanniang,
you, a woman, became the commander of the Bingjing Office.
It was the Emperor's grace
that set a precedent for women to serve as officials in the Song Dynasty.
Don't push your luck.
Lord Cui,
so you know the Emperor set a precedent for me.
My entire Chu family is fiercely loyal.
How dare you frame us?
If you talk about face, Lord Cui,
what kind of face do you even have?
Take them all back to the Imperial City Department prison.
Sir,
let's go.
Go check over there.
Search over there, hurry.
The guards are catching up.
We must leave now.
I'll lead the way.
Nothing over there.
Look over there.
Go.
Meng,
wait a moment.
Lord Chu can't walk anymore.
How are you?
Can you hold on?
Why did you save me?
I already told you.
If my daughter were still alive,
she would be about your age.
You really look like my daughter.
If you keep following me,
we might die together.
If I can keep you safe,
does your promise to help me find my daughter
still count?
Of course it does.
Sir,
we have to leave right now.
Meng,
since I saved your life,
I have a favor to ask.
Tell me.
I won't refuse.
I am currently
working for Lord Chu.
This is the wound medicine I carry with me.
Apply it to her later.
I...
I also...
Meng.
I think Lord Chu
is the person I'm looking for.
Please.
Be careful, my lord.
My lord.
There's a rock here.
Let's sit down and rest.
Be careful.
Are you hurt this badly?
Should we apply some medicine first?
Then I'll trouble you to apply medicine for Lord Chu.
I'll go find some firewood nearby.
Take good care of him.
Is Lord Chu a man or a woman?
I'll go scout the way.
Call me if you need anything.
I'll go with you.
Meng Qian,
come help.
Where are you going?
You and Uncle Chai dare to break out of prison?
Don't you want your sister-in-law and sister to live?
You can hardly save yourself now, my lord.
Yet you still want to threaten me?
You think I can't do anything to you?
I only agreed
to the old man,
that's why I'm applying medicine for you.
Otherwise, I would have run away long ago.
You better heal your wounds quickly.
I'm in a hurry to go home and find my sister-in-law and sister.
Wait.
Give me the belt.
Belt.
Go help Zhu Zitong start a fire.
I'm not your subordinate.
You...
I found a silk letter
on one of them.
I've been working hard for you.
But you?
You always look down on me.
Uncle Chai.
Come out.
You are very weak
right now.
So?